Alan W. Steelman papers, Inclusive: 1960-2003, Bulk: 1973-1976
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1965-1976, undated; 8
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Cassette tape
  - 93rd Congress, 1973-1974; 1
    - Aaron, Hank, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Age Discrimination, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Aid to Members-Elect, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Alaska Pipeline, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Amendment of Section 1130 of Social Security Act, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Americans Missing in Action, 1973-1974 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Animal Traps, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Annual Social Security Wage Reporting, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Architectural Barriers, 1973-1974 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Assistance to Israel, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Atomic Energy Information, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Autism, 1973-1974 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Barter Foreign Aid for Minerals, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Beach Resources, 1973-1974 (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Big Thicket, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - Boxcar Shortage, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - Broadcast Licenses, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - Budget Reform, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - Busing, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - CabComm Opportunities for Spanish-Speaking, 1973-1974 (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - Cabell Federal Building, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 21)
    - Chancellor Industries, 1973-1974 (Box 116, Folder 22)
    - Commemoration of the 100th Birthday of Churchill, 1974 (Box 116, Folder 23)
    - Commend Sakharov and Solzhenitsyn, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 24)
    - Commerce (1 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Commerce (2 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Commerce (3 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Commerce (4 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Commerce (5 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Commerce (6 of 6), 1973-1974 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Commerce and Trade Reform, 1973-1974 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Committee Reform, 1974 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Communications CB’s, 1973-1974 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Communications Media (1 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Communications Media (2 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Communications Media (3 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Communications Media (4 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Communications and John Doggett Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Condemn Terrorist Killings in Israel, 1974 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Congratulations on Election to 93rd Congress, 1972-1973 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Congressional Advisory Legislative Line (CALL), 1974 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Congress, H.B. 133, 1974 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Congress (1 of 2), 1974 July-November (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Congress (2 of 2), 1974 July-November (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Congress, 1974 May-June (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Congressional Baseball Game, Baseball Cards, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Congressional Baseball Game, Baseball Cards, Alan Steelman, 1974 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Congressional Pay, 1974 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Congressional Record, 1974 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Congressional Record, 1973-1974 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Congressional Salaries, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Correspondence (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Constituent Correspondence (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Constituent Correspondence (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Constituent Correspondence (1 of 2), 1974 January-February (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Constituent Correspondence (2 of 2), 1974 January-February (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Constituent Correspondence (1 of 2), 1974 March-April (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Constituent Correspondence (2 of 2), 1974 March-April (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Consumer Affairs (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Consumer Affairs (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Cosigned Letters, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Cosigned Letters, 1974 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Costs of Legislation, 1974 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Cross-Florida Canal, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Cuyahoga Park, 1974 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Cyprus Conflict, 1974 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Davis, Sammie Jr., 1973-1974 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Disclosure of Financial Information, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Eastern Wilderness, 1974 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Ecology (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Ecology (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Ecology (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Ecology, 1973-1974 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Ecology, 1974 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Economic Stabilization Resolution, 1974 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Economic Summit, 1974 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Economy (1 of 7), 1974 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Economy (2 of 7), 1974 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Economy (3 of 7), 1974 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Economy (4 of 7), 1974 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Economy (5 of 7), 1974 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Economy (6 of 7), 1974 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Economy (7 of 7), 1974 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Economy (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Economy (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Economy ROBO No. 129, 1974 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Education, 1974 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Eisenhower College and Rayburn Library, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Elderly Americans, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Elk Hills Naval Petroleum Reserve, 1973-1974 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Emergency Home Mortgage Credit, 1974 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Emergency Medical Services, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Energy Patents, 1973-1974 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Energy Research and Development, 1973-1974 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Energy Research and Development Administration, 1973-1974 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Energy Research and Development Program, 1973-1974 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Environmental Agenda, 1973-1974 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Employee Stock Ownership Program, 1973 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Employee Stock Ownership Program, 1974 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - FDA Consumer Vitamin Labeling (1 of 6), 1973 (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - FDA Consumer Vitamin Labeling (2 of 6), 1973 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - FDA Consumer Vitamin Labeling (3 of 6), 1973 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - FDA Consumer Vitamin Labeling (4 of 6), 1973 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - FDA Consumer Vitamin Labeling (5 of 6), 1973 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - FDA Consumer Vitamin Labeling (6 of 6), 1973 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - FDA Vitamins and Mineral Supplements, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Federal Employee Unions, 1973 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Foreign Investment in the US, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Full Financial Disclosure, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - GI Bill Extension, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Gold Ownership, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Guam National Historic Park, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Harrington, Mike (ETA), 1973 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Health (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Health (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Helium Conservation, 1974 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Highways, 1973-1974 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Highways (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Highways (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Highway Trust Fund 80%, 1973-1974 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Home Health Services Act, 1974 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Homeowners Energy Conservation, 1973 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - House-Authorized Budget, 1973 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Import-Export Bank, 1974 (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Inflation, 1974 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - International Economics, 1974 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - IRS-Independent Agency, 1974 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Joint Committee on Intelligence Oversight, 1974 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Joint Funding Simplification Act, 1974 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - King Statue, 1974 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Land Use Planning (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Land Use Planning (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - LBJ Memorial Grove, 1973-1974 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Legislation (1 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Legislation (2 of 2), 1973-1974 (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - Legislative Issues, 1973-1974 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Lobbying Reform, 1974 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - Little, Vertie Jr., 1973 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - Marigold as National Flower, 1973 (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - Menominee Indians, 1973, 1975 (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - Mexican and WWI Veterans Pensions, 1974 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Middle East Ceasefire, 1973 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Minority Staffing, 1973 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Nametag, 1974 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - National Center on Rape Prevention and Control, 1974 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - National Economy (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - National Economy (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - National Economy (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - National Parks Wilderness, 1974 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - National Security Classification System, 1974 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - New National Park Studies, 1974 (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Nursing Home Patients Bill of Rights, 1973 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Ohio & Erie Canal, 1973 (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - OMB Confirmation, 1973 (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - OSHA Reform, 1973 (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Overdue Debts, 1973 (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Paperwork Burden, 1974 (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - Phase IV Hospitals (1 of 3), 1973-1974 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Phase IV Hospitals (2 of 3), 1973-1974 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Phase IV Hospitals (3 of 3), 1973-1974 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Political Affairs, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Postal Supervisors Arbitration (H.R. 7202), 1973 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - President, Campaign Reform, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Price Stability, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Privacy (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Privacy (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Prohibit Civilian Surveillance by Military, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Prohibit Polygraph Tests for Employment, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Property Tax Relief, 1973 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Public Affairs, 1973 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Public Disclosure of Foreign Travel, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Public Disclosure of Lobbying, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Public Documents, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Public Service, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Questionnaires, 1973 (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Questionnaire Tabulations, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Radiation Therapy, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Repairs to Residence, 1973 (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Repeal Economic Stabilization Act, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - Reporting Requirements in Legislation, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Republican Conference, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Rule to Consider Committee Reform, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Save Outdoor America, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Second-Class Mail Rate Increases (H.R. 8929), 1973 (Box 130, Folder 18)
    - Second-Class Postage Rates (H.R. 1248), 1973 (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - Select Committee on Aging, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 20)
    - Senior Citizen Interns, 1974 (Box 130, Folder 21)
    - Service, Employment, Redevelopment (SER), 1973 (Box 130, Folder 22)
    - Social Security, 1973 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Social Security Reforms, 1974 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Social Services, 1973 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Soft Drink Bottlers, 1973-1974 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Southwest Airmotive (James Nelson Co.), 1973-1974 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Soviet Energy Investments, 1974 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Soviet Jews, 1973-1975 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Summer Internship Program, 1973 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Support President in Middle East Action, 1973 (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Surface Mining, 1973 (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Surveillance Practices and Procedures Act, 1974 (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - Task Force on Economic Revitalization, 1974 (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - Tax on Fuel Consumption, 1973-1974 (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Televise Impeachment Proceedings, 1974 (Box 131, Folder 14)
    - Transfer Reporting from OMB to GAO, 1974 (Box 131, Folder 15)
    - Transportation (1 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 131, Folder 16)
    - Transportation (2 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - Transportation (3 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Transportation (4 of 4), 1973-1974 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Transportation Truck Weight (No. 5312), 1974 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Turkish Opium, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Singles Taxes, 1973 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Urban Homesteading, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Veterans Benefits, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Vietnam MIA’s, 1973 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation, 1973 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - War Powers, 1973 (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Water Pollution Funds, 1973 (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Watergate Reports, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Wild and Scenic Rivers, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - Women in Combat, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - Women in Military Academies, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 15)
    - Wounded Knee Victims Compensation, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 16)
    - $500 Savings Interest Tax Deduction, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - 8th Grade Questionnaire Results, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - 94th Congress, 1975-1976; 2
    - Additional Sentence for Felon with Firearm, 1975 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Aircraft Museums, 1975-1976 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Americans in Mexican Jails, 1975 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Amtrak, General, 1975 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Animal Traps, 1975 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Arab-Israeli Conflict, 1975-1976 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Architectural Barriers, 1975 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Architectural Barriers, 1975-1976 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Beta Sigma Phi Week, 1976 (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Big Thicket, Legislative Taking, 1975-1976 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Big Thicket, Ralph Yarborough Unit, 1975 (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Bottler’s Bill, 1975-1976 (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Budget Resolution, 1975 (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - Business (1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - Business (2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - Business, 1976 (Box 133, Folder 16)
    - Busing Amendment, 1975-1976 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Car Fuel Economy Tax, 1975 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Civilian Health and Medical Program of the Uniformed Services (CHAMPUS) Coverage, 1975 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Change in MIA Status, 1975 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Child Care Regulation, 1975-1976 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Chinese Accountability for American MIA’s, 1975 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Classification, 1975 (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Coal Leases, 1975 (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Communications, 1975 (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Communications, CBer’s ROBO (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Communications, CBer’s ROBO (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - Communications, CBer’s ROBO, 1974-1976 (Box 134, Folder 12)
    - Communications, Media, 1975 (Box 134, Folder 13)
    - Communications, Public Broadcasting (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Communications, Public Broadcasting (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Communications, Public Broadcasting (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Confidentiality of Tax Returns, 1975 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Congressional Record, 1975 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Congressional Record Subscriptions, 1976 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Congressional Approval of Regulations, 1975-1976 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Congress Pay Raises, 1975 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Constituent Concerns, 1975-1976 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Consumer Affairs (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Consumer Affairs (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Consumer Affairs, 1975 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Cosigned Letters, 1975 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Cosigned Letters, 1976 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Cost to Taxpaying Family of Legislation, 1975 (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Crane Postal Service Bill, H.R. 4951, 1976 (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Deficit Spending, 1975 (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Deregulation of Natural Gas, 1976 (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - Discrimination Against Physically Disabled, 1975 (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Displaced Homemakers, 1976 (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Ecology, Clean Air Act, 1976 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Ecology, Environment Study Conference, 1975-1976 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Ecology, Toxic Substances, 1976 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Economy (1 of 4), 1976 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Economy (2 of 4), 1976 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Economy (3 of 4), 1976 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Economy (4 of 4), 1976 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Economy, Budget (1 of 4), 1976 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Economy, Budget (2 of 4), 1976 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Economy, Budget (3 of 4), 1976 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Economy, Budget (4 of 4), 1976 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Education Savings, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Electronic Surveillance, 1975-1976 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Elk Hills Petroleum, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Elk Hills Petroleum, 1976 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Emergency Health Benefits for the Unemployed, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Environmental Study Conference, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Ecology (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, Ecology (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, Ecology (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - EPA- Ecology (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, Ecology (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - EPA and Emission Controls ROBOs, 1975 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Employee Stock Ownership Plans, 1975-1976 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Estate Taxes, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Evidence in Rape Trials, 1975 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Evidence in Rape Trials, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Executive Agreements, 1975 (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Farm Estate Taxes, 1975 (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Food & Drug Administration, Consumers, Vitamins, 1975 (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - Federal Aid to New York City (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - Federal Aid to New York City (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Federal Election Commission, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Financial Disclosure (1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Financial Disclosure (2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Financial Disclosure, 1975 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Flint, George, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Food Aid and Family Planning, 1975 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Aid ROBOs, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Franking Privileges of Former Members, 1975 (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Freedom from Military Surveillance, 1975 (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Good Neighbor Day, 1976 (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - Government Bureaucracy, 1975 (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - Government in the Sunshine, 1975-1976 (Box 140, Folder 13)
    - Government Procurement Policy, 1976 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Guam Constitution, 1975 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Guam Historic Park, 1975-1976 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Hawk Mission to Jordan, 1975-1976 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Health (1 of 4), 1975 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Health (2 of 4), 1975 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Health (3 of 4), 1975 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Health (4 of 4), 1975 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Health (1 of 3), 1976 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Health (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Health (3 of 3), 1976 (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Health, Insurance, 1976 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Hell’s Canyon, 1974-1976 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Veto, 1976 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Hispanic Americans Resolution, 1976 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Home Health Care, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - House GOP Legislative Program, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Impoundment of 701 Funds, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Indiana Dunes, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Indiana Dunes, 1976 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Inflation, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Interest Payments on Government Deposits, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Interns from Vocational Schools, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - IRS Legal Fees, 1976 (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - Israel in the United Nations, 1975 (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - Issues (1 of 3), 1975 April-June (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - Issues (2 of 3), 1975 April-June (Box 142, Folder 16)
    - Issues (3 of 3), 1975 April-June (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Issues, 1975 April-July (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Issues, 1976 August (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Issues, 1975 August-September (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Issues (1 of 4), 1976 January-April (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Issues (2 of 4), 1976 January-April (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Issues (3 of 4), 1976 January-April (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Issues (4 of 4), 1976 January-April (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Issues, 1976 July (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Issues, 1976 June (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Issues, 1976 May (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Issues, 1976 September-December (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Jack Anderson’s Congressional Ratings, 1976 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Jobs Creation Act, 1975 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Joint Committee on Intelligence Oversight, 1975-1976 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - King Statue, 1975 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Land and Resource Conservation (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Land and Resource Conservation (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Land and Water Conservation Funds, 1975-1976 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Land Use Planning Act, Hearing Dates and Witness, 1975 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Land Use Planning Act, H.R. 3510 and Memos, 1975 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Land Use Planning Act, Organization Comments, 1975 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Land Use Planning Act, Press Comments, 1975 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Land Use Planning Act, Steelman’s Speeches, 1975 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Land Use Planning Act, Witness Testimony, 1975 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Legislative Issues (1 of 2), 1975 January- March (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Legislative Issues (2 of 2), 1975 January- March (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Legislative Issues, 1975 October-December (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Loans and Tax Credit for Insulation, 1975 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Lobbying Reform, 1976 (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Lobbying Reform, 1975 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Lower Age for Congressman, 1975 (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Manassas Park, 1975-1976 (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Mandatory Retirement, 1975-1976 (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Medicare Coverage Expansion, 1975-1976 (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Medicare Nursing Reimbursement, 1975 (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Minority Business Development, 1976 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - National Commission on Social Security, 1976 (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - National Commission on Social Security, 1975 (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - National “Employ the Older Worker Week”, 1976 (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - National Family Week, 1975-1976 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - National Respiration Therapy, 1975-1976 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - National Respiration Therapy Week, 1975-1976 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Natural Trails System, 1976 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - New River, 1976 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - No Political Recommendations for Civil Service, 1975 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - No Time Limit on Veteran Education, 1976 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Office of Hispanic Affairs, 1976 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Older Americans (1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Older Americans (2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Older Americans, 1976 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Outpatient Radiation Treatment Coverage, 1975 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Panama Canal Zone Employment, 1976 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Patient’s Bill of Rights, 1975-1976 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Patriotism, “Our United States-Help Save It” (tape recording), 1975 (Box 147, Folder 15)